Raul Uriostegui

raulujr@gmail.com

San Diego, CA



https://www.linkedin.com/in/raulu-cse/ in

Software Engineer

EDUCATION

BACHELOR'S DEGREE Computer Engineering University of California, San Diego | La Jolla, CA 2017 - present

EXPERTISE

- Java
- HTML
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- SASS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- Node.is

CERTIFICATIONS

Front End Mastery Clever Programmer Front End Mastery Bootcamp Nov 2021

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Developed front end web applications using HTML for the backbone, CSS for styling in conjunction with Tailwind CSS as a framework and SASS as a preprocessor. Experienced in working with JavaScript by showing problem solving skills on Code Wars. Integrated HTML and CSS with JavaScript framework React.js and Next.js to create dynamic web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SPIS Mentee

University of California, San Diego Computer Science and Engineering Department | La Jolla, CA | Jul 2017 – Aug 2017

- Attended an intense summer coding program for 5 weeks
- Learned programming languages like Python and Java to help prepare me for future coursework at the university
- Constructed a final project which was a web application about fashion

Teacher Assistant

ThoughtStem | San Diego, CA | Jul 2018 - Sep 2018

- Assisted a teacher at summer coding camps for K-12 youth
- Oversaw students and facilitated camp activities
- Answered questions and guided students through coding curriculum

Triton Community Leadership Institute Mentor

Communication and Leadership - Center for Student Involvement at UCSD | La Jolla, CA | Apr 2018 - July 2019

- Mentored first-generation freshman that are from underrepresented communities/backgrounds
- Led social justice workshops to prepare mentees to become leaders on campus
- Met mentees on a 1 to 1 basis each quarter at least twice to ensure their success as a freshman